<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Computer Technologies Project</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Recent content on Computer Technologies Project</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 20:01:29 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>http://example.org/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:31:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/about/</guid><description>Hello, my name is Guillaume Van Putten, I am a 5th year student at the French school ESILV. I am currently an exchange student in Riga Technical University, in the Department of Electronics and Telecommunication.
This website is a project for the course Computer Technologies in Telecommunciation. It&amp;rsquo;s a kind of CV where I share my professional experiences and the projects I could take part in.</description></item><item><title>GPS application</title><link>http://example.org/school_project/gps_application/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 20:01:29 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/school_project/gps_application/</guid><description>SafeWay is a GPS application that favors safety instead of speed for the itineraries it offers and which also leans on its community to signal and report suspicious or dangerous behaviors.
There are around a thousand assaults that occur every day in France. This number continues to increase by more than 10% each year for assaults on women of 18 to 30 years of age. At the same time, women’s speech liberation movements appear on social networks, such as #metoo or #balancetonporc.</description></item><item><title>Robot host</title><link>http://example.org/school_project/robot_host/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 19:59:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/school_project/robot_host/</guid><description>DeVinci Fablab and DaVinciBot are two associations that cohabit in the Fablab space located on the 5th floor of the Learning Center at the Pôle Léonard de Vinci. DeVinci Fablab is an association of makers who are there to help students in their personal and professional projects while managing the 3D printing park. DaVinciBot is a robotics association which is represented by two projects that progress from year to year, namely the humanoid robot InMoov and the Robotics Cup.</description></item><item><title>Engineering diploma</title><link>http://example.org/education/esilv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 18:14:40 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/education/esilv/</guid><description>At the end of high school, I chose ESILV to continue my studies in the field of engineering, a generalist school focused on digital. I spent 3 years seeing courses on very diverse subjects, like mechanics, mathematics, computer science or electricity. In the 4th year I chose the IoT and Security major, wanting to orient my skills around embedded systems.</description></item><item><title>Private teacher</title><link>http://example.org/professional_experience/completude/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/professional_experience/completude/</guid><description>Thanks to complétude, a service that connects tutors with children or students in academic difficulty, I was able to take care of middle and high school students. I taught math, physics and chemistry, which requires patience and listening skills, but I really enjoyed helping these students and helped them improve their grades, but most importantly I think I taught them better work methods.</description></item><item><title>Embedded systems engineer intership</title><link>http://example.org/professional_experience/blet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/professional_experience/blet/</guid><description>I did this internship at BLET Measurement Group, a metrology company that resells measuring instruments and offers calibration services. Researching and understanding new products is essential to remain competitive in this market. In addition, the company is constantly improving its calibration laboratory to be able to respond to all types of requests.
In this context, associated with another intern and under the supervision of Thibaut Champenois, the CTO of the company, the missions I was entrusted with during this internship were in the field of research and development, with 3 main subjects</description></item><item><title>Exchange programme</title><link>http://example.org/education/rtu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/education/rtu/</guid><description>As part of my engineering course, I had to do an academic exchange abroad, after several complications related to the health situation around Covid-19, I was finally accepted for a semester in Riga in the Riga Technical University. In this school I chose the Faculty of Electronics and Telecommunication in order to increase my skills and knowledge in the field of embedded systems. For this exchange programm, I am taking courses on web development, FPGA, electronic design, cryptology and wireless communication.</description></item><item><title>High School</title><link>http://example.org/education/high_school/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/education/high_school/</guid><description>3 years in which I learned basic stuff and though about an engineer cursus, as I was good in scientific subjects.</description></item><item><title>Maintenance technician intership</title><link>http://example.org/professional_experience/marin_d_eau_douce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/professional_experience/marin_d_eau_douce/</guid><description>As part of the ESILV&amp;rsquo;s teaching programme, we must complete an internship of at least 12 weeks, there are no restrictions for this internship, the aim is to acquire experience in a company, whether technical or relational. For my part, I did this internship in the company Marin d&amp;rsquo;eau douce, a start-up company that rents boats without licence for small groups, located in the pound of La Villette in the 19th district of Paris.</description></item></channel></rss>