<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Professional_experiences on Computer Technologies Project</title><link>http://example.org/professional_experience/</link><description>Recent content in Professional_experiences on Computer Technologies Project</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/professional_experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Private teacher</title><link>http://example.org/professional_experience/completude/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/professional_experience/completude/</guid><description>Thanks to complétude, a service that connects tutors with children or students in academic difficulty, I was able to take care of middle and high school students. I taught math, physics and chemistry, which requires patience and listening skills, but I really enjoyed helping these students and helped them improve their grades, but most importantly I think I taught them better work methods.</description></item><item><title>Embedded systems engineer intership</title><link>http://example.org/professional_experience/blet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/professional_experience/blet/</guid><description>I did this internship at BLET Measurement Group, a metrology company that resells measuring instruments and offers calibration services. Researching and understanding new products is essential to remain competitive in this market. In addition, the company is constantly improving its calibration laboratory to be able to respond to all types of requests.
In this context, associated with another intern and under the supervision of Thibaut Champenois, the CTO of the company, the missions I was entrusted with during this internship were in the field of research and development, with 3 main subjects</description></item><item><title>Maintenance technician intership</title><link>http://example.org/professional_experience/marin_d_eau_douce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/professional_experience/marin_d_eau_douce/</guid><description>As part of the ESILV&amp;rsquo;s teaching programme, we must complete an internship of at least 12 weeks, there are no restrictions for this internship, the aim is to acquire experience in a company, whether technical or relational. For my part, I did this internship in the company Marin d&amp;rsquo;eau douce, a start-up company that rents boats without licence for small groups, located in the pound of La Villette in the 19th district of Paris.</description></item></channel></rss>