<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Educations on Computer Technologies Project</title><link>http://example.org/education/</link><description>Recent content in Educations on Computer Technologies Project</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 18:14:40 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Engineering diploma</title><link>http://example.org/education/esilv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 18:14:40 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/education/esilv/</guid><description>At the end of high school, I chose ESILV to continue my studies in the field of engineering, a generalist school focused on digital. I spent 3 years seeing courses on very diverse subjects, like mechanics, mathematics, computer science or electricity. In the 4th year I chose the IoT and Security major, wanting to orient my skills around embedded systems.</description></item><item><title>Exchange programme</title><link>http://example.org/education/rtu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/education/rtu/</guid><description>As part of my engineering course, I had to do an academic exchange abroad, after several complications related to the health situation around Covid-19, I was finally accepted for a semester in Riga in the Riga Technical University. In this school I chose the Faculty of Electronics and Telecommunication in order to increase my skills and knowledge in the field of embedded systems. For this exchange programm, I am taking courses on web development, FPGA, electronic design, cryptology and wireless communication.</description></item><item><title>High School</title><link>http://example.org/education/high_school/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/education/high_school/</guid><description>3 years in which I learned basic stuff and though about an engineer cursus, as I was good in scientific subjects.</description></item></channel></rss>